

LUONG TAN PHAT

Front-End Developer

- **19/09/1995**
- Male
- **6** 0983.007.839
- **■** tanphat9324@gmail.com
- Tp.Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam
- i https://tanphat9324.github.io/portfolio/

TECHNOLOGY

- React JS
- Redux
- Javascript
- Node JS
- Redux
- HTML5 & CSS3
- o Git



Hi! My name is Phat. I'm extremely passionate about web development especially Frontend Development, helping businesses and improve their online presence.

Currently, I graduated with a Bachelor of Electronics and Communications Engineer Technology Degree 2 years ago, I have finished Front-end Development Course at CyberSoft Academy and had over 6 months of working experience in ReactJs. I currently aim to learn as much as I can in a work environment and to further my own abilities in a professional setting.



EDUCATION

SAI GON TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY

08/2013 - 08/2017

Major: Electronics and Communications



WORK EXPERIENCE

IPTP NETWORKS

06/2018 - PRESENT

JUNIOR NETWORK ENGINEER

Engineers are responsible for handling technical requests & complaints via internal ticketing system, troubleshooting problems & escalating too the next level of support, working with documentation.

- Works with Router, switch, Access point devices...
- Monitoring and operating the global network system.

PHUONG NAM TELECOM & MINH PHUC TELECOM

08/2017 - 04/2018

IT SUPPORT

Resolve problem to:

- Network troubleshooting, including wired and wireless devices.
- -Receiving support requests directly from users via emails or logging tickets to the helpdesk system and confirming the reception or requests to users in a timely manner.



PROJECT

PROJECT 123PHIM (PROJECT IS PROGRESSING...)

https://github.com/tanphat9324/Project_Movie

Tech stack: ReactJs, Git.



CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Certified Network Professional Route (CCNP Route): Good

Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA) 05/2018

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA): Excellent 03/2018

07/2018